<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <!--FTPSite sa-->
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>Satan Arise News / Updates</title>
    <link>http://www.satanarise.com/index_uk.php</link>
    <description>Channel of Satan Arise with the news, interviews and reviews!</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>info@satanarise.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@satanarise.com</webMaster>
    <image>
      <title>Satan Arise News / Updates</title>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/index_uk.php</link>
      <url>http://www.satanarise.com/pics/sa.jpg</url>
      <width>100</width>
      <height>89</height>
    </image>
	<item>
<title>Review of Icestorm - Contes De La Vall De Glaç</title>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 17:56:23 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[The band has released Catalan Icestorm finally their first full length, which will be released officially on 24 November. Contes De La Vall De Glaç be available in two versions, the digital where you can listen all the tracks on the album and physics that will further the narrative voices are linking some issues and bring the listener to follow the story told in this conceptual work. Also, as an added value we can enjoy the voice of this narrative that we find very familiar and is none other than the voice that turned to Gandalf in the film "The Lord of the Rings". ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/icestorm_contesdelavalldeglac.html</link>
<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
<category>Reviews</category>
</item>
	<item>
<title>Review of L'Endeví - An Eternity</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 8 Nov 2012 10:06:14 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Second work of L'Endeví from Valencia after their debut album When I Desire Something, You Can't do Anythingin 2010, two years later has seen the light An Eternity, that as a good second album tries to settle the position of this interesting , as little band. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/lendevi_aneternity.html</link>
<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
<category>Reviews</category>
</item>
	<item>
<title>Review of Jose Rubio's Nova Era - Nova Era</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 5 Nov 2012 11:40:02 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Although in Spain the guitar solo projects do not have the desire of the majority of the public, there are still musicians who dare and well in the opinion of a server. This is the case of Jose Rubio, after going through groups like Trilogy, Warcry, Megara or Dunedain, the guitar virtuoso decides to create his own group José Rubio's Nova Era in which dwell with his instrument and his ideas. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/joserubiosnovaera_novaera.html</link>
<author>Toni Nieto &lt;toni.nieto@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
<category>Reviews</category>
</item>
	<item>
<title>Review of Ereb Altor - Gastrike</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 10:00:09 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Ereb Altor is undoubtedly one of the key bands in the little known world of viking-doom metal. This band was formed in Gävle, Sweden, about 1990, although it was not until 2003 that they released their first demo called "The Awakening", but we will focus on his latest work that came to light this year 2012 through Napalm Records. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/erebaltor_gastrike.html</link>
<author>Metxo &lt;metxo@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
<category>Reviews</category>
</item>
	<item>
	<title>Review of Avven - Kastalija</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 09:34:38 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[This band focuses on a Slovenian folk metal with a unique sound of their origin, Slavic influences are present in almost all of the disk. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/avven_kastalija.html</link>
	<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Derrota - Con Dos Erres</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 09:31:07 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[Formation of Blanes, Girona, we presented a CD of rock and roll raw, live, classic rock tinged, urban rock, and very combative themed. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/derrota_condoserres.html</link>
	<author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Antalgia - Perception Of Reality</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 09:43:08 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[From Lleida Antalgia released his first job Realm Of Reality, as little work that is nothing short of amazing. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/antalgia_perceptionofreality.html</link>
	<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Biosfear - Antes De Que Todo Cambie</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 9 Oct 2012 10:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[I'll start from the end. When I finished listening to the CD, I said ... OK? .. I have to poke back. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/biosfear_antesdequetodocambie.html</link>
	<author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Grave Digger - Clash of the Gods</title>
	<pubDate>Sat, 6 Oct 2012 17:53:10 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[The fifteenth work of Germans Grave Digger, entitled Clash of the Gods, the band returned to the present. This time the chosen concept is Greek mythology. Under this premise, as typical in the work of the Germans, we are presented with an album continuity. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/gravedigger_clashofthegods.html</link>
	<author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>
	<item>
	<title>Review of Arkgabriel - Arkgabriel</title>
	<pubDate>Wed, 3 Oct 2012 11:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[Very good presentation that offered this work, an edition digipack, very carefully worked, with a fairly complete libretto and striking, with good artwork and photographic work. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/arkgabriel_arkgabriel.html</link>
	<author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Chaos Theory - Bio-Death</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 09:18:36 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[The Thrash metal have a new awakening, and there are many national and international bands that opt to regain strength and aggressiveness of thrash either in its most classic form or giving another approach with other influences. Chaos Theory have chosen the classical variant in their debut Bio-Death. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/chaostheory_bio-death.html</link>
	<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Tankard - A Girl Called Cerveza</title>
	<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 10:31:29 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[The Germans Tankard presented his new album, the fifteenth, titled A Girl Called Cerveza. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/tankard_agirlcalledcerveza.html</link>
	<author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Pictured - The Strand Of Time</title>
	<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 10:17:25 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[Pictured The French have released their first full length album, The Strand Of Time stamped Klonospehere. Pictured was formed in 2007 with band Aponium members and after five years of history, a demo and an EP titled The Dwelling have embarked on The Strand Of Time. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/pictured_thestrandoftime.html</link>
	<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
	<item>
	<title>Review of Fangorn - Where the Tales Live On</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 10:10:49 +0100</pubDate>
	<description><![CDATA[Second work of Russians Fangorn, Where The Tales Lives On, after his last album Mysterious Land two years ago. A group completely unknown, and further demonstrates the amount of emerging bands come from Eastern European countries, often in styles ranging from folk to the most extreme black. ]]></description> <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/fangorn_wherethetalesliveon.html</link>
	<author>Sergi &#8220;Helloween&#8221; &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
	<category>Reviews</category>
	</item>	
    <item>
      <title>Interview with A Sound Of Thunder</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 13:04:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/asoundofthunder_08_12.html</link>
      <author>Akasha &lt;akasha@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Interview with A Sound Of Thunder that have released this year theis second album Out Of The Darkness.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Mpire Of Evil - Hell To The Holy</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 10:04:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/mpireofevil_helltotheholy.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Mpire Of Evil is not like the others new bands in the world of metal, in fact despite being a greenfield project, the nobel qualifier so far as they have left their youth. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Testament - Dark Roots of Earth</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 09:04:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/testament_darkrootsofearth.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It was the early years of the 80's. In San Francisco, California, is beginning to take shape a new music scene, later known as the Bay Area. Bay Area referred to a series of bands formed in San Francisco that began to shape a new style, later known as Thrash Metal. The Bay Area may be separated into two waves. In the first coming bands like Metallica (originally formed in Los Angeles, it was not until his arrival in San Francisco, along with the entry into the band Kirk Hammett and Cliff Burton, when the band finally takes off), Exodus, Lääz Rockit, Slayer, and Possessed (his album Seven Churches (1985) is regarded as the first mix album Thrash with a new style, later known as Death Metal). These patents first bands leave their influences. The New Wave of British Heavy Metal, particularly in the vocal melodies and the Punk (much more evident in the scene in New York), were the basis of those bands that form a new style. With the second wave, the sound of the "new" bands change. Groups like Testament, Forbidden, Heathen and Death Angel. The songs of these bands begin to be longer and more complex in their structures. Guitars more virtuous and neo-classical sound. The influence of the NWOBHM became more evident and almost completely disappeared Punk compositions. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Sinheresy - The Spiders and the Butterfly EP</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 09:48:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/sinheresy_thespidersandthebutterfly.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[From Italy comes an EP, the first work in the study of Sinheresy, as The Spiders and the Butterfly. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Meden Agan - Erevos Aenaon</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 09:35:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/medenagan_erevosaenaon.html</link>
      <author>Guillermo Riesgo &lt;guillermoriesgo@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I have wanted to hear a Greek band began to break over the last year between symphonic metal scene and will participate in the prestigious and exclusive Femmale Metal Voices Fest in Belgium. Your Name: Meden Agan and its hallmark is its singer Iliana Tsakiraki, a big girl like the ones we usually see at the opera. Formed in 2005 in Paris by guitarist Koutsogiannopoulos Diman and two demos and one LP that went more or less unnoticed, the band finally removed in 2011 their second album Erevos Aenaon. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Psideralica - Neophobia?</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 09:42:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/psideralica_neophobia.html</link>
      <author>Ahbyss &lt;ahbyss@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Over time Psideralica is slowly becoming a band delicatessen in our country. Since their previous album 'Engel Der Nacht' return to the fray after several changes enveloping us in a climax industrial metal rock and pop dyes. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Soundcrawler - The Sandcrawler</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 11:21:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/soundcrawler_thesoundcrawler.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[With a futuristic cover we find the self-produced debut album of French Soundcrawler for which little information I could find. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Zona Oscura - El Placer De Fracasar</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 11:25:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/zonaoscura_elplacerdefracasar.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Zona Oscura starts operations in 1999 in the Asturian town of Aviles. The only original member who even today remains in the band is Tonay (Carpe Diem, Badulake, The Box, Santo Jueves) on vocals and guitar. After winning the first prize in the Concurso de Grupos y Cantantes de Castrillón in 2004 Uga (Badulake) on bass join to the band. In 2006 they recorded the song " No somos nada " for the album " Tributo a La Polla Records dende Asturies " and the demo " Más triste es de robar ". In December 2009 they are joined by Christian (Die Fighting, N'Arba, Exitus, Breaking Silence, Jacky Trap, Rhein Metall, Sangre, The Seventh Sign) giving rise to the current formation. Together they win the prize for best production and composition in the 8º Concurso de Música en Directo of the youth association Abierto Hasta el Amanecer in Gijon in 2010. During 2011 they recorded their first album, " El placer de fracasar ", he sees the light in March 2012. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Sobredosis - Ángel Negro</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 07:17:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/sobredosis_angelnegro.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The Madrid Sobredosis, after 27 years since his last recording, present Ángel Negro, which means his third studio work. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Nina of 69 Chambers</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:54:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/69chambers_07_12.html</link>
      <author>Akasha &lt;akasha@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Interview with Nina, singer and bassist of 69 Chambers , who recently published their second album Torque .]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Zarpa - Las Puertas Del Tiempo</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 09:02:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/zarpa_laspuertasdeltiempo.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The Valencians Zarpa returned to the attack with a new album entitled Las Puertas Del Tiempo ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Nöud - Ausente</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 08:50:49 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/noud_ausente.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[With over fifteen years, the locals Nöud finally have recorded their first full-length entitled Ausente. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Crudo - Cicatrices</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 08:38:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/crudo_cicatrices.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band starts walking Asturian Crudo back in October 2008 after the germinal band Volvone participation in the contest pf rock city of Oviedo and Luis formed by Melero (Sauze, Los Débiles, Ojo Negro, Volvone) on bass and vocals, Gansan (Hard Spirit Volvone) on guitar, Sergio Álvarez (Knock Out!!, Tierra de Nadie, Volvone) on drums, Victor Vivar (Madera Rock, Zin Lissy, Volvone) on guitar and vocals. In early 2009 they get into Pin-Gui studies under the supervision of Julio Cernuda to record what would be his first contact record, a demo of eight songs that take Name " Somos Crudo " and also to serve as an introduction before the national rockerio, opens the doors of competition Gijón " Abierto hasta el Amanecer ", where they reach the final and get the award for musical quality. In May last year Gansan guitarist left the band and was replaced by Rubén Álvarez (Madera Rock, Darna, Xeliba, Tejedor, Herbamora, Magamalabares, FMM Now return to the fray with its first large disk, the " Cicatrices " that we present and was recorded and mixed in studies of NDKE Foundation of Modern Music by Ruben Alvarez Aviles between the months of October 2011 and February 2012. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Katana</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2012 19:10:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/katana_06_12.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Katana has released their second album Storms Of War, we have beem talking with Johan Bernspång and Susanna Salminen, singer and bass player fo Katana.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Sacramento - Weight Of Sin</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 09:50:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/sacramento_weightofsin.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Chile, like the rest of South America is a country that consumes a lot of metal and much more intense than in Europe and some bands like Criminal and have managed to reverse the jump and enter the European market, do you get Sacramento ? Of course the ingredients have been planted, to see how you harvest. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In this moment new videoclip</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 10:00:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#derrama</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Available the new video for the song Blood, the same title than the album]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angelus Apatrida anounces the dates of their presentation tour of The Call</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 10:00:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#angelus</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[They are preparing a set list with all their musical legacy]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New confirmation for the Xmas Fest 2012</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 10:00:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#xmas</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It's the band Skyclad who joins Lonewolf, Nightmare, Astral Doors, Ñu, Iron Savior and Elvenking]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Saturday on the hall KGB of Bcn, II aniversario de Metaleros de Catalunya</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 10:00:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#metaleros</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[With the shows of Mike Zágora, Katarsick, Karlahan, Nyctophobia, Drakum and Health Healer]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napalm Death, new videoclip</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 10:04:43 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#napalm</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band presents new video for the song The Wolf I Feed of their last disc, Utilitarian]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Herman Frank - Right in the Guts</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 08:58:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/hermanfrank_rightintheguts.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[In case anyone does not know this guitarist, we present to Herman Frank. German guitarist. He has served on Victory from 1986 to present. He formed the band Moon 'Doc played with Sinner. With Accept from 1982 to 84 to return in 2005 and returned in style in 2009 until today. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of La Espera - Con Luces Y Sombras</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 08:23:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/laespera_conlucesysombras.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Began in 2002, but it was not until a couple of years later they began to give concerts. In 2007 they recorded their first album in the Engine Room of Albacete with producer Pepe Cifuentes. The album lead by name " Y sentir la mañana " and whose road show led them to play at the Viña Rock 2008. That same year, giving a giant step in his musical career since his song " Quisiera volver en otro momento " tuning the program ends up being " Ponle freno " that airs on TV A3. In 2009 under the auspices of the city of Albacete recorded the song " No hagas planes en septiembre", which became the official anthem of the town fairs. Their second album " Con luces y sombras " as recorded in late 2011 but has now been when he finally sees the light. Again have had the Pepe with the production of Cifuentes, technical known for his work with Chucho, Mercromina or Hermano Lobo. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of A Sound of Thunder - Out Of The Darkness</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 09:54:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/asoundofthunder_outofthedarkness.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[A Sound Of Thunder, sci-fi film of 2005 ... and start a blog if it were film, but A Sound of Thunder is also the name of Washington's four musicians have just released their second album, Out Of Darkness. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videoclip, advance of the new album of Saurom</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jul 2012 13:45:37 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#saurom</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It's the song Cambia el mundo. The album will be entitled Vida]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prometheus, trailer of the new videoclip</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jul 2012 13:45:37 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#prometheus</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be the song Mil años y un día]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leo Jimenez, contest and news conference</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jul 2012 13:45:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#leo</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Next July 17th, the singer will present their first videoclip and the rest of the band for lives shows]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Luca Turilli's Rhapsody - Ascending to Infinity</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jul 2012 09:37:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/lucaturillirhapsody_ascendingtoinfinity.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[After all the controversy generated by cleavage of Rhapsody Rhapsody of Fire first and then Luca Turilli's Rhapsody, sharing practically logo and even originally one of the musicians as drummer Alex Holzwarth, we were a little afraid of the supersaturation of the style after the release of Rhapsody of Fire. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Sphere anuncia nuevo vocalista</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:09:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#secret</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[He is the excellent singer Michelle Luppi]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ankor in Japan, next gigs and new video</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:09:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#ankor</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Last May they release their last video, it's a version of the song from Adele Someone Like you]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saratoga explains the cancelation of their gig on Córdoba</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:08:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#saratoga</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of differences with the organization of the Guitar Festival in Cordoba payment guarantees]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in the line-up of Northgard</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:08:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#nothgard</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[After the departure of the keyboardist, joins a third guitar player: Skaahl]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New material of The Great Destroyer X</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:08:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#tgdx</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It's the showcase that will present together with Life Vectors in September]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kivents anounces the signature of a new band: 3797</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#kivents</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The hardcore band from Guipuzcua is part of the agency roster]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaser trailer of the new video of In this moment</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#inthismoment</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It's the song Blood]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grave reveals their cover and the tracklist of their new album</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#grave</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be entitled Endless Procession Of Souls]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Request to the Costa de Fuego!</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:05:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#tlr</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band from Ibiza has win the place to play there]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pan De Higo prepares their fourth album</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:05:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#pandehigo</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be entitled Otros menesteres]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nachtmystium, new online song</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:05:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#nachtmystium</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The Chicago BlackMetal band will released a new disc Silencing The Machine
You can listen to the song onBorrowed Hope And Broken Dreams on the next link: Borrowed Hope And Broken Dreams]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wormed signs with Third Eye Society</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:05:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#wormed</link>
      <author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The veteran band from Madrid, become part of the agency's roster ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Mind, Daily Record</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jul 2012 19:05:05 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias15.html#darkmind</link>
      <author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band recorded in the studios of La Casa de la Música de Fuenlabrada and under the baton of Ix Valieri (037, Infernoise, Angels From Hell) as a producer recorded her first album entitled "Kaos". 
The album features the collaboration of Rown Houland (Infernoise, Clockwork) ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Diabulus In Musica - The Wanderer</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 Jul 2012 09:59:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/diabulusinmusica_thewanderer.html</link>
      <author>Guillermo Riesgo &lt;guillermoriesgo@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I have wanted to talk about Diabulus in Musica, Pamplona's band is making its way in the world, performing in several editions of the festival Belgian Metal Female Voices, the most important specialized in bands led by women.<br />And to understand that success must have heard this, his second album "The Wanderer". ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Leithian - Sin Límites</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 4 Jul 2012 09:52:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/leithian_sinlimites.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlimited surprise that offered Leithian from Valencia. After a very good debut album " Voces de Libertad " in which the band was a great alternative power metal, very fast and very guitar-leave us impressed with a second disk that have not taken a step forward, but at least two or three at least. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Last Prophecy - 2.0.13</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 3 Jul 2012 09:16:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/lastprophecy_2013.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[After a long downtime for the band, it has been since 2006 until 2011, the Navarrese back with their third album called 2.0.13. A record that has generated considerable excitement and the lovers and followers of the band will not disappoint at all, it is the best work of his career. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Contrabanda - Trece</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 3 Jul 2012 08:08:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/contrabanda_trece.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrabanda history dates back to 2005 under the auspices of Robert Shy (drums) and Soto (bass). Not until 2007 when he closes the triangle instrumental Juankar entry on guitars. After trying out several singers, the band is finally completed in mid 2009 with the signing of Javi, whose vocal range is what I was looking for the group. After several months touring the circuit of theaters in Madrid in early 2010 known music producer Emilio Mercader (purposely, Desperation, Peter Andrea, Cool, Surge), engaging in the project as a component. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Manowar - The Lord Of Steel</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 2 Jul 2012 09:49:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/manowar_thelordofsteel.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[In Italy we find a band called Nanowar, which practices a comical power metal or metal Freak, which obviously are dedicated to parody different bands, different features of exaggerating them. Obviously, only the name of the band, it is clear that Manowar are one of those bands, perfect on the other hand, to parody.I do not know whether to celebrate 30 years since the release of that legendary Battle Hymns (1982), Manowar released this The Lord of Steel, which, from its title seems a self parody. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Zonaria - Arrival Of The Red Sun</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 10:50:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/zonaria_arrivaloftheredsun.html</link>
      <author>Sergi “Helloween” &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Arrival Of The Red Sun is the third album of Swedish Zonaria, after four years of silence. Change in training, is now dealing Max Malmer Bass, and seal change, have signed by France's Listenable Records and these Zonaria defined as "the saviors of the Swedish death metal." Perhaps too pompous words from the pen of a publicist wanting to cause controversy to draw attention to the band. Not whether to save the Swedish death metal, if they needed to be saved, but making it clear Arrival Of The Red Sun, is that you must stay with the name Zonaria if you like melodic death metal. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Spectral</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 12:41:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/spectral_06_12.html</link>
      <author>Sergi Helloween &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The German Spectral have released their fifth album this year, Gateway To Death, and this year will be playing at the Defenders Of Steel festival.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Winter's Verge - Beyond Vengeance</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 10:05:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/wintersverge_beyondvengeance.html</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Cyprus has never been a country that has generated great metal bands, and like all statistics, is ready to break and this is Winter's Verge ham manager who just released their fourth album Beyond Vengeance through the German label Massacre Records. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Paradise Lost - Tragic Idol</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 09:51:19 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/paradiselost_tragicidol.html</link>
      <author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[After more than 20 year career, 12 albums, style changes, comings and goings, it looks like Paradise Lost, return to the right path in this their thirteenth album. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Westhia - Westhia</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 09:56:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/westhia_westhia.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Formed in Asturian lands back in 2004 after the separation of In-Sanity bands (heavy thrash) and Ashtma (thrash / death) and for a period of time the repertory concert featuring westhia were songs they had composed for these two bands. After many trials they see that it works and are slowly emerging new issues. Initially started as a quartet with Chus (bass), Robert (drums), Diego (guitar and vocals) and Victor (guitar and vocals). It is late 2007 when it enters "The Jevo" to the battery by leaving the post Robert, who takes full control as a vocalist. They have two demos that are pre-drive Westhia (2007) and Fallen (2010). ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamelot presents new singer</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 19:02:05 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[He is Tommy Karevic, who was sung before on Seventh Wonder]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterly cover and advance of the new album</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 16:33:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#masterly</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be entitled Sin Identidad and you can listen to a medley]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Masterly</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 16:33:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/masterly_06_12.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Taking advantage of the imminent departure of his new album "Sin Identidad", we chatted a while with the guys from Masterly to meet them and we were introduced to their new vocalist Sergi Perea.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Menzia - Way To Nowhere</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 09:36:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/menzia_waytonowhere.html</link>
      <author>Topillo &lt;topillo@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The alternative progressive metal band from Barcelona "Menzia" return to the fray with a second studio "Way To Nowhere" after "Lamb's Skin for the Wolf". A new study of seven subjects, about thirty minutes in which proposed a style and image that escapes from the convention itself and systematization of any style or genre. A job and a band itself remains unchecked any stylistic box that is daily making itself a singularity in a very attractive and appealing to the listening public. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videoclip from Sombras</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:02:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#caronte</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Available the videoclip of Caronte, single of the folk metal band, Sombras]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Available the new work of Beethoven R</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:02:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#beethoven</link>
      <author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Soon will anounce new dates. You can see their new videoclip here]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Places Never Imagined is the new song of Absolute Factory</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:01:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#absolute</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It's the musical project of Ramón Cabilla]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First dates for the tour of Hybris</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:01:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#hybris</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The national tour will be entitled From lost to the InstinTour]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new album of Lesbian Bed Death for sale next June 25th</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:01:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#lesbian</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band will start a tour around UK]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out Date for the new album of Embellish</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:01:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#emmbellish</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be released next September 3th through Crystal Eyes Records and it will be entitled Blindead]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality Grey back on the road with a new management deal</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:01:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#reality</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[K2Music Management proudly announces the sign of the band from Italy]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darksun: recording live DVD</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:01:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#darksun2</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The recording will be next July 6th on Gijón]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview to Nocturnia</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 19:00:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/nocturnia_06_12.html</link>
      <author>Akasha &lt;akasha@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Building output Nocturnia new album, we wanted to make the band a few questions and carry out the interview with Jose Maria Roldan, drummer of the band.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Gauntlet - Stubburn</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 07:50:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/gauntlet_stubburn.html</link>
      <author>Javier Casal &lt;javier.casal@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[If something is true of Gauntlet is that your best virtue is perseverance, because after a few years of career, with several lineup changes, especially in the vocals, two demos and two CD, s long-term, we get to blows fresh from the oven of the studies "New Life" (Madrid), and mastering via the "Fascination Street Studios" (Sweden), which is number 3, and honoring the adage, "the third time lucky .....? "could be. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Sôber - Superbia</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 08:13:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/sober_superbia.html</link>
      <author>Topillo &lt;topillo@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Sôber, the progressive formation of the brothers Escobedo returned with an album beat "Superbia" that shows the maturity of training, the genius in the lyrics and sound very accomplished, unique not leave anyone indifferent. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Factor 19 - Campo De Sueños</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 07:13:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/factor19_campodesuenos.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Little is known of the whereabouts of former members of Factor 19 and is that little information can be drawn from them on the web and even less promotional sheet. Just who are locals and are defined as "Brutal Pop", but do not worry, do not take offense at the head hands swearing in Aramaic that this is an assertion made in plan joker. Eventually they recognize that theirs is to recover the spirit of hard rock and heavy metal of the eighties and early nineties. As a company is not bad but how they do it? I'd say that much of each other. "Campo De Sueños" was recorded at the Greek Records between May and June 2011 and is produced by Anne Paranoid. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Rizon - Masquerade</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 08:54:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/rizon_masquerade.html</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Rizon released last February, his third studio album, Masquerade. As often happens with bands that do not start with the push of a major label, they come with some albums released, in this case two, and knowing nothing of its existence. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Struendo - Maldito Seas</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 22:49:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/struendo_malditoseas.html</link>
      <author>Tatotitotu &lt;info@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[First is called 90-60-90 and a little later Esbirros. It was early 2007 when gathered in an old garage finally adopted the name of Struendo. The band was composed by Cesar Vega on vocals and rhythm guitar, José María Martínez "Tapi" on lead guitar, Antonio Pulido on bass and Manuel Chico on drums. In October 2008 launche a demo self released of five songs "Resiste Vol.1", recorded in Sevilla quite home and although their sound was not very good, yes it helped them to be released to the public in form of first dates and participation in various music competitions. In June 2010 the progress of the battery suffer as a result of discouragement caused by a false contract signed with an agency to make a record. That fact was about to dissolve the band. Fortunately the entrance of David Muñoz on drums, the death metallers from Violencia, brought a breath of fresh air to the group that decided to continue his musical journey with more vigor and renewed strength. In April 2011 they recorded this album in the studios Engine Room by Manuel Lorca Torroglos where groups have also recorded as Blindfall, Lilith or Skizoo. For various problems delayed the departure of the cd until finally sees the light in January of this year. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sergio Martínez cames back to 037</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 14:02:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#037</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[He will play again on Madrid next June 24th]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koma: Official notepress</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 16:56:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#koma</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Brigi Duke will leaves the band]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subterráneo Management will work with Dark Eternity</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 16:56:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#darke</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, the band is still presenting their album Selenia]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens on the Road: Starts the Crownless's tour</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 10:46:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#crownless</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Starts on Torrejon de Ardoz, and the next will be on Murcia. Check dates and listen to the new single Ravens in the Storm]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tierra Santa signs with Calle Underground</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 11:46:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#tierrasanta</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Soon will anounce new dates. You can see their last videoclip]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.A.0: Ends the recording of the new album</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 11:46:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#da0</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[...Cero is the chosen name for this LP with eleven songs]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sound Storm presents new keyboardist</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 11:46:02 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#soundstorm</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Before the release of their new album, they present Davide Cristofoli]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Talesien - Silencio (7.5/10)</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 10:44:59 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/talesien_silencio.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[ buen lanzamiento para todos los públicos, y es que lejos de encasillarse en un estilo con un abanico de público reducido, apuestan por dar rienda suelta a las influencias y llegar a un espectro más amplio de seguidores]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Kreator - Phantom Antichrist</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 10:20:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/kreator_phantomantichrist.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Kreator are definitely one of the greatest thrash metal bands that has given the history of this music. Pioneers and purest representatives of European Thrash, have a history full of great albums, since that Pleasure to Kill (1986), the hurtful Terrible Certainty (1987) or one of the best works of the genre as Extreme Aggression (1989), all them indispensable for understanding the evolution of a style. A magnificent and undervalued work and Renewal (1992) and his return to the roots with Violent Revolution (2001) are clear examples of the quality treasured by Mille Petrozza and yours. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Eldelvar - Once Upon A Beer</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 09:40:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/eldelvar_onceuponabeer.html</link>
      <author>Topillo &lt;topillo@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Eldelvar is a folk metal band from Barcelona has released his first album "Once Upon a Beer". About fifty minutes which let us listen to an interesting, bold and unpretentious. "The Flight of The Phoenix", an orchestrated intro gives way to "When The Moon cries Blood" single from the band presented via on-line before I saw the light of this latest album. A piece very folky, fun, perfect for dancing, kick and jump on the track / goblin battlefield. The third theme "Crusaders" is perfect for raising their fists and humming the melodies of flutes and violins in unison. "Frogs" one of my favorite songs on the album. Very funny, horny and more than one takes us to the mythical and legendary land of Hyrule, meeting and not a mysterious boy named "Skull Kid" dancing with laughter and laughter. The fifth song "Victory Celebration" is a very successful cover of the final song of "Star Wars: Return of the Jedi" which leads to "Bastards of Babylon" another of my favorite songs of the album with a very catchy tune special concerts and meetings metaleras folk. "Through The Snow" I consider it one of the most interesting and most beautiful lines throughout the album. One of the areas are neglected voices prevail torn and the Pussycats; Eldelvar get a piece off the record intimate and typically presents the folk metal. Nice work indeed. "The Stone Reader" and "Eldelvar", the last two tracks of "Once Upon a Beer" follow the same line that characterizes the band, noting in a more folkie first and the second a more epic and fast. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New single from Leithian</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:18:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#leithian</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It's the song Angel Seductor]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change bassist and new album from Vision Divine</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:18:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#vision</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be entitled Destination Set To Nowhere and will be released on Setember]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaunlet show case acoustic</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:18:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#gauntlet</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover will will have an interview on the Noise Off Festival next Monday 19th]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second birthday of Metaleros de Catalunya</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:18:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#metaleros</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The association has organized a celebration with a gig with the bands Mike Zágora, Katarsick, Karlahan, Abrahel, Drakum and Health Healer]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dünedain will continue with their Tour de la Rabia</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:18:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#dune</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[5 new dates for this summer]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album of Macbeth completed</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:18:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#macbeth</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[It will be entitled Wiedergänger]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Saratoga - Nemesis</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 09:09:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/saratoga_nemesis.html</link>
      <author>Devilsoldier &lt;devilsoldier@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The difficulty, though in this country more, not to arrive, if not maintained. Like many others, Saratoga had its moment of glory. Anything over. Clearly, nothing lasts forever, but there are always reasons for things. Saratoga is also clear that, for matters internal to the band, he could not take that success and succumbed. The output of Jero Ramiro and Leo Jimenez ordered the band to mediocrity, unfortunately, so abundant in these parts. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Headon</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 8 Jun 2012 16:56:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/headon_05_12.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[On May 12th, we met the band from Murcia, Headon, and they presented to us their new singer "Tihan Muñoz", and we have talked about the departure of Andy Martinez to 037, and their future plans presenting their last album and recording a new one]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Andy Martínez, singer of 037</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 8 Jun 2012 16:56:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/andy_05_12.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[On May 12th, we met Andy Martinez, to know his impressions of his early days fronting the band as vocalist and know a bit more about him.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The organization of Costa de fuego rectifies</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:19:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#costa2</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The organization has overcome certain logistical problems and reach the promised 50 bands]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manakel listen to the second single</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:19:18 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#manakel</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Second single in advance of Luz]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santelmo new video</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:18:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#santelmo</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[t's about the recording moments of Roma a las puertas]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offtopic presents their next shows</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:18:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#offtopic</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[There will be the last with Cristian on drums]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wereworld looks for guitar player</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:18:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#wereworld2</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Albert Toledano leaves the band]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setge looks for guitar player</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:18:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#setge</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The extreme metal band from Catalonia is serching rythm guitar]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorod confirmed fot the HellFest</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 15:18:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#gorod2</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The bands are being confirmed]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Raven's Gate</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 12:27:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/ravensgate_04_12.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[On April 28 interviewed Raven's Gate, a young band that has just been released their firt live near Sylvania and Darkblazzers. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Moonloop - Deeply From The Earth</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jun 2012 09:34:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/moonloop_deeplyfromtheearth.html</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[From France by Listenable records I have found out the existence of Moonloop, which are from Barcelona and gives me a sense of amazement and embarrassment, how can you not ....? ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Crimson Cult - Tales Of Doom</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 6 Jun 2012 06:50:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/crimsoncult_talesofdoom.html</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Tales Of Doom, second album of the Austrians Crimson Cult, a band that moves into the more classic Heavy Metal influences power and even a touch more progressive. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed the bands that will act on Costa de Fuego</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 5 Jun 2012 16:01:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#costa</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[14 new bands confirmed, like Dünedain, Dry River or Ankor]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nachtmystium cover and new song</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 5 Jun 2012 16:01:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#nachtmystium</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band that mixes black and psicodelia, shows the cover of their new album Silencing Machine]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Nocturnia - Sin Retorno</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 5 Jun 2012 13:12:05 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/nocturnia_sinretorno.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[On first listen that this new work, called Sin retorno, the band suggests many changes, new shades and on first impression, it leaves a taste of mouth clear: It's the best job of the band from Toledo]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leo Jimenez belies its entry into Mägo</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 4 Jun 2012 15:51:58 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#leo</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The excellent vocalist use social media to publicly deny rumors about his future]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Astral - Mundo Perdido, Mundo Prohibido</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 2 Jun 2012 03:17:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>www.satanarise.com/uk/novedades/astral_mundoperdidomundoprohibido.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[From Valencia comes this work of Power Progressive Metal!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkania presents the new band members</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 3 Jun 2012 03:16:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#arkania</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[They are Jesús Chevron and Rafa Delgado, guitar player and drummer]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darksun shows the cover of their new album</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 1 Jun 2012 03:16:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#darksun</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Artwork of Memento Mori has been made by Daniel Alonso - Digital Art]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cavus working in a new album</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 1 Jun 2012 03:13:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#cavus</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The disc, without name yet, has the first songs titles]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New videoclip by Gorod</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 1 Jun 2012 03:13:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#gorod</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The song is Elements and Spirit from the new album A Perfect Absolution]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wereworld nominees for the independent music awards</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 03:13:51 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#wereworld</link>
      <author>Sergi "Helloween" &lt;sergi@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[The band is a finalist in the category for best metal album]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blacktroll presents the III ed. de Troll Festival</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 1 Jun 2012 03:13:51 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/noticias_uk.html#blacktroll</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Next June 30th DooMination, Sygma, Offtopic and Masterly will offer a show, on the way of become classic]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official notepress by Arkania</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 03:13:51 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/noticias/noticias14.html#arkania</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>News</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Jonathan Sánchez leaves the drums and Godo the guitars]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Ronnie Romero</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 2 Jun 2012 19:10:04 +0200</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.satanarise.com/uk/entrevistas/ronnie_06_12.html</link>
      <author>Vic Salda &lt;vsaldanya@satanarise.com&gt;</author>
      <category>Interviews</category>
      <description><![CDATA[With the imminent release of the CD of Jose Rubio's Nova Era was talking with Ronnie Romero, lead singer of the band, who talks about this project and others that also participate. ]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>